amen uh once again happy
Sabbath today's uh
message uh is really really an important
one
um I uh um my prayer is that this
message will speak to your heart
um the title it it sounds a little bit
uh well let me just tell you the
title uh the title of the message is the
wormwood
deception the wormwood deception I hope
that captures your
attention because uh you know as God's
people we are warned about all kinds of
deceptions that will come into go to
God's church at the end of time is that
right
um and
yet uh as I've been studying this
subject I personally believe that this
deception is perhaps one of the greatest
deceptions uh facing God's
people and so uh I really want you to
focus on this
message and uh allow the Holy Spirit to
speak to your heart let's pray Heavenly
Father we come before you at this time
lord asking to for you to please speak
to our hearts Lord take these
words and bring life to them Lord open
our
eyes and father please help us to At
Last be saved in the
Kingdom Lord I pray I pray that you
would help me to make this message
clear and that it will
impact everyone who hears it
in Jesus name we pray
amen I invite you to turn with me in
your Bibles to the Book of Revelation
chapter
8 Revelation chapter
8 and uh we will begin
reading in verse 10 Revelation chapter
8 and verse 10
the Bible
says and the third Angel sounded and
there fell a great star from Heaven
burning as it were a lamp and it fell
upon the third part of the rivers and
upon The Fountains of
waters and the name of the star is
called
wormwood the name of the star is called
whatever everyone wormwood and the third
part of the waters
became
wormwood and many men died of the waters
because they were made
bitter now we're going to do a little
bit of uh just we're going to put a
couple verses together to help you gain
an understanding of what this verse
These two verses are talking about in
The Book of Revelation there are a
series of
sevens uh three of those series of
sevens are the seven churches the Seven
Seals and the Seven trumpets what are
they everyone the seven churches the
Seven Seals the seven trumpets
now these sets of sevens unfold
simultaneously so the first church
unfolds simultaneously with the first
seal which unfolds simultaneously with
the first trumpet the same with the
second the same with the third all the
way down and so when we get to the third
trumpet um we could actually go to the
Third Church to get a better idea of
what is happening under the third
trumpet does that make sense so far yeah
all right so let let's just hold our
place here we want to go over to this
church it's uh the third church church
excuse me it's found in Revelation
chapter 3 Revelation chap 3 rather
Revelation uh chapter that's right
Revelation chapter
3 Revelation Chapter
2 that's right that's what you heard
Revelation Chapter
2 and
um let's look at verse 12 Revelation 2
and verse 12 the Bible says say to the
angel of the church in pergamus write
these things save he which has the sharp
two-edged sword I Know Thy Works where
thou dwellest even where Satan's seed is
and thou holdest fast my name H has not
denied my faith even in those days
wherein Antipas was my faithful martyr
who was slain among you where Satan
dwells but I have a few things against
you because you have there them that
hold the doctrine of balum who taught
BAC to cast a stumbling block before the
children of Israel to eat things
sacrificed unto idols and to commit
fornication so hast thou also them that
hold the doctrine of the nians which
thing I hate repent or else I will come
unto thee quickly and fight against them
with the sword of my
mouth the Third Church pergamus would
parallel the third trumpet we just read
about in Revelation chap 8 the Third
Church per pamus had an issue had a
problem and the problem was uh if we
were to sum it up we would simply say
the problem of the third church was
compromised these seven churches Seven
Seals and seven trumpets
represent different periods of time in
the church age if you will the pergamus
church would represent the period of
time in which compromise began to enter
into God's Church especially under a man
by the name of Constantine how many of
you are familiar with that history all
right this is where uh paganism began to
infiltrate God's
church under the church third church
period the Church of pergamus so when we
read about this uh uh this thing called
wormwood under the third trumpet we know
that it must have something to do with
compromise since it parallels the third
church if you're with me so far just say
amen amen all right so uh uh let's see
what happens again under this third
trumpet the Bible says a star falls from
heaven and it falls into the waters and
the waters became what bitter okay now
let's check out what Waters symbolize in
the scripture jump over with me to the
Book of Revelation chap 22 revelation 22
and verse 1 and 2 revelation 22 verse 1
and2
this star falls into the rivers and the
rivers become bitter revelation 22 verse
1 and 2 the Bible says he showed me a
pure clear as Crystal proceeding out of
the Throne of God and of the land so
here we see a river and that river is
called the River of Life now this River
of Life is is really symbolic of you
know the reward of the righteous at the
End of Time how many of you want to
partake of the River of Life amen so far
so good jump back with me one chapter to
Revelation
21 Revelation 21 and verse 6 he said
unto me it is done I am the Alpha and
the Omega the beginning and the end I
will give unto him that is a thirst of
the Fountain of the water of what life
freely so the Fountain of the Water of
Life the River of Life uh uh symbolizes
in essence the the gospel the what
everyone the gospel how many of you are
thirsty for the Water of Life yes we
want to drink in fact Christ invites us
to come unto him to drink let me share
with you just a few more verses uh
notice with me Zechariah chap 13 and
verse one Zechariah 13 and verse one and
let me encourage you do not be
bored let me encourage you do not think
what does this sermon have to do with me
me just wait we're getting there
Zechariah
13:1 the Bible says in that day there
shall be a fountain open to the House of
David and to the inhabitants of
Jerusalem for sin and for uncleanness
this verse symbolizes the fact that the
gospel is equated to a fountain that
purifies from sin
amen Jeremiah 17 and verse 13
Jeremiah
17 and verse
13 the Bible tells us here that God
himself is that Fountain Jeremiah
17 verse 13 oh Lord the hope of Israel
all that forsake thee shall be ashamed
and they that depart from me shall be
written in the Earth because they have
forsaken the Lord the found
of what Living Waters all right so now
that we've got that hammer down we
remember that under this third
trumpet a star falls and it turns the
waters into what it turns the waters
bitter the name of the star is
worm wood
wormwood in a sense we might come we can
come to the
conclusion that whatever happened under
this third trumpet was like was
something that made the
gospel
what bitter yes something that made the
gospel become bitter to the taste of
people and so we know that under this
third trumpet you know various things
were were going on we know know that
there be began to be compromise in God's
church let me share something with you
Deuteronomy chapter 29 Deuteronomy
chapter 29 I want you to notice Verse 18
and
19 Deuteronomy
29 Verse 18 and 19 the Bible says here
Deuteronomy
29 18 and
19 in fact we we'll start with verse
16 the Bible says for you know how we
have dwelt in the land of Egypt how we
came through the Nations which you pass
by and you have seen their what
Abominations and their Idols wooden
Stones silver and gold which were among
you lest there be any should be any
among you any be any among you man or
woman or family or
tribe whose heart turns away this day
from the Lord Our God to go and serve
the gods of other nations lest there
should be among you a root that beareth
G and what
wormwood listen carefully in the Old
Testament God warned that that we should
not uh adopt the practices of the
Heathen Nations because it would produce
something called
wormwood wormwood the root of wormwood
now the word wormwood means bitterness
what does it mean everyone bitterness so
God had this concern that if any of the
children of Israel began to compromise
that somehow or another it would bring a
root of bitterness within
Israel that's the
concern now in Revelation chapter
8 we see that that as a result of the
church beginning to compromise with
Pagan practices what entered into the
church bitterness the
gospel was
made bitter that which should have been
pure that which should have been lovely
that which should have been how many of
you like sweet
things yeah I know some it's bad like
but you know sweet things are good I
don't like bitter things how many of you
like bitter things no no no bitter
things make you want to stay like oh I
want to say yeah you
when you taste something bitter what
does your face
do you know some of us come to church
like
that wow that's interesting we we don't
like bitter things generally I'm not
saying that all bitter things are bad
but we don't like bitter things
generally but here we see that the
gospel that which should have been sweet
that which should have been inviting was
made bitter why because of compromise
specifically within God's
church are you are you hearing me not
outside of God's church now this fell on
the rivers on the bodies of water which
symbolize the gospel so here is
something that is happening inside the
church which tended to
bitterness in Matthew 7:1 15 Matthew 7
verse1 15 I want you to notice the words
of Jesus Matthew 7 verse 15 the Bible
says beware of what false
prophets which come to you in sheep's
clothing but inwardly they are what
ravening woles H uh Paul himself wrote
In fact turn it with me Acts 20: 29 acts
chap 20 20 and verse 29 I want you to
see what Paul himself wrote Acts 20
verse
29 here's what Paul says for I know this
that after my departing shall Grievous
wolves enter in among you not sparing
the flock also of your own selves shall
men arise speaking what kind of things
perverse things to draw away disciples
after themselves Jesus and Paul both War
learned that sometime in the future
Grievous walls would come and they would
uh uh teach perverse things they would
compromise there would be apostasy and
this is exactly what we see happening
under this third trumpet there is this
growing apostasy within God's Church
which in essence brings about the
condition where the
gospel which is supposed to be pure
becomes what bitter
bitter you say Pastor what what does
this have to do with me what does it
have to do with us how is this the
greatest
deception of the day you
see I want you to imagine what could
have made the church back in that time
period
bitter because because what you have
happening is apostasy coming into his
church can that make can that bring
bitterness to the gospel
when you begin to see apostasy going on
in the church you know what was also
happening persecution began to happen
and let me ask you something is it a
pleasant thing to be persecuted by your
brother or
sister no that can be quite a bitter
experience how many of you would
agree you know how many of you expect
persecution to come from outside the
church yeah when we signed up for
Christianity we signed up for
persecution I was oh those
non-christians are going to hate us we
were prepared for
that yes but what many of us were not
prepared
for what was to see apostasy and
compromise happening where on the
inside let me tell you something I'm
going to speak like really Frank to you
today because uh I've been in Adventist
now for
202 thank you
years and
uh I've experienced some really really
really crazy
things how many of you have experienced
crazy things as Adventists how many of
you have been like wait a minute wait
this is God's church right and you ever
had that like wait wait wait we we are
in church this is a Sabbath day right
like this could not have just happened
in the church on Sabbath this I've had
some
experiences and I'm not speaking of
myself alone because I know you have had
experiences let me tell you something uh
when compromise and apostasy begins to
come into church and and it could be
apostasy of
Doctrine yeah but it can just be
behavior yeah and when these things
happen they bring about a bitterness to
the gospel that which is supposed to be
inviting that which is supposed to be I
can't wait to get up and go to church on
Sabbath makes you kind of like have that
bitter face ah do I have to go anyone
ever experienced it do I have to go do I
have to face the people who are supposed
to be on the same
page listen it it is it is a
mind-blowing thing when you have
Minister backbiting against
Minister it is a mindblowing thing when
you begin to look inside the church and
see all kinds of bitterness going on
even Ministry to
Ministry you I was talking with someone
the other day just in the last coup last
week or so and this person is in a
Ministry a and he was sharing with with
me listen guys I'm speaking frankly with
you right now is that okay can me just
be frank he was speaking he's he's he's
an Adventist and he he's in a Ministry
and he was telling me how how this other
Ministry Adventist Ministry I is is
seeking to put down his ministry so that
this other Ministry can have more time
out in the field ministering and we were
sitting on the phone talking and I'm
like what this is this is happening in
God's Church
how can we have backbiting and murmuring
even amongst those who are claiming to
forward the
work and beloved I'm telling you
something we are in a situation right
now within the Adventist Church where we
are seeing guess what Ministry pointing
finger at Ministry Ministry pointing
finger at Ministry and member pointing
finger at
member we are in a scary place in our
church
today you see we have a right to be
concerned about apostasy we have a right
to be concerned about false Doctrine we
have a right to be concerned about
murmurings and and jealousy and all
these things let me share something with
you I want you to notice with me Isaiah
chapter 5 verse 20 Isaiah chapter 5 and
verse
20 Isaiah 5 verse 20 notice what the
Bible says
here Isaiah 5: 20 the the Bible says woe
unto them that call evil what
good like we as as Adventists need to be
on the lookout because the apostasy
means you're calling evil what good let
me tell you something how many of you
how many of you just wins just when you
hear something that is apostasy you just
go oh it makes you bitter
yeah it makes you like oh this is God's
Church why is this going on in God's
Church in God's house why can't we all
be on the same page yes yeah it gives
you that sense of and and and yes we
ought to be uh indignant when we hear
evil being called
good you see beloved when we apostas
eyesee when we when we
compromise something begins to happen
bitterness begin begins to
come into God's church I want you to
think about
Jesus do you know the Jews were in a
condition in which they were calling
evil good do you know that they were in
a condition where they were like it is
better for us to crucify this man that
the whole nation does not
perish in their minds they thought they
were doing what good they were calling
evil good
are we at that place right now do we see
this happening within God's church right
now absolutely we see it happen but
check this out it's not just about you
know apostasy and look at this person
teaching that Doctrine and this person
denying that Doctrine you
see can you have your own personal
apostasy yeah you know what is apostasy
it is it is turning your back on God
really can you have some days where you
turn your back on
God you
shouldn't but can
you yeah there there are some days you
you just go into your own personal
compromise your own personal apostasy
and guess what that does for your life
that bring the result of that is
bitterness in your
life you see Satan wants to use
bitterness he wants to use wormwood to
actually destroy check this out James
chapter 3:
6 James chapter 3 and: 6 and and and I
want you to notice James chapter 3: 6
it's talking about the tongue and in
verse 6 it says this the tongue is a
fire a world of iniquity so is the
tongue among our members that it
defileth the whole body and sth on fire
the course of hell and it is set on fire
of hell for every kind of beasts and of
birds and of serpents and of things in
the sea is Tamed and has been tamed of
mankind but the tongue can no man tame
it is an unruly evil full of deadly
poison therefore bless we God even the
father and therewith curse We Men which
are made after the similitude of God out
of the same mouth proceedes blessings
and cursings my brethren these things
ought not to be so does a fountain send
forth at the same place Sweet Water and
bitter why
when our tongues are used to glorify God
on one
hand but speak ill of our brother or
sister on the other
hand you know what that is it's
wormwood it's
wormwood one of the greatest deceptions
our church is facing today is that many
people are drinking
wormwood oh listen the
listen uh
um the root is not the same thing as
the
fruit okay did you catch that just now
the root is different from the fruit so
there is a root of bitterness that's
what we read in Deuteronomy 29 unless a
root of bitterness bears fruit so the
root is different from the fruit so
listen here's the root we just
discovered the root is
compromise
apostasy people doing you know within
God's Church doing bad to one another
speaking ill of one another that's the
root but the fruit is something
different you see
beloved how many of us when we
are challenged with a bitter event
we
ourselves
be anyone ever struggle with
bitterness why because what someone did
to me was so
bitter the root that the
fruit
becomes me coming to church like this
yeah I become
bitter the the purpose of wormwood is to
cause other people to do stupid and
crazy things that will in turn make you
become bitter anyone struggle with
wormwood don't raise your
hand yeah come on you're probably
thinking right now I remember what that
guy did to me last week I remember what
what what this in the world we can
handle it yeah the world is supposed to
do that but in the church we're like no
the church we're on a different level
this should not be going on in God's
house why is this happening why are they
being so mean to
me and before you know it you have
become
infected with the wormwood
deception now now you
yourself are
bitter you see
not only can we experience these bitter
things in in the church you know this we
can have those bitter events of Life
yeah anyone just have those bitter
events of Life
sickness the loss of a loved
one a and in that
bitterness you can begin to ask yourself
where was God when I was going through
this yeah
where was God When when when when you
know the church members were doing this
to me or where was God when when I was
you know going through this experience
or going through that experience let me
tell you how many of you have struggled
with
wormwood yeah you can raise your hand
now you can raise your hand now yeah all
of us have struggled with wormwood we go
through the these experiences let me
tell you something I'm I'm going to be
using this in a the sermon some other
time some other way so you're going to
hear it again last week we were in Wala
Wala and uh we were speaking I was
speaking and uh you know at tante and
the girls were uh towards the back of
the church and so after I finished
speaking um I I made an appeal then I
went down to talk with some people and
then a tante came over to me and she we
were talking a little bit there were
other people around and she was like oh
by the way have you seen Genesis CA she
went to the
bathroom uh you know about 10 minutes
before your appeal and I haven't seen
her and so by the time she tells me this
like at least 25 to half an hour has has
already passed and we know Jen you know
Genesis she's not especially in a
strange Place she's not going to go
somewhere disappear and then like you
know just be gone that's that's not what
you does so you know I'm like what so
I'm talking with some people and I'm
like okay you know uh hey uh let me
finish talking a little bit later I got
to go find my daughter and we begin
looking around the church and at first
I'm like I'm not going to say anything
anybody I'm just going to look and I'm
looking I'm looking and a minute passes
by two minutes pass by and you know what
begins to happen as a
parent you begin to
wonder wait a minute she's going to the
bathroom she went alone we're in a
strange
place and all kinds of thoughts but I'm
still trying to be calm because you know
what we're in God's house
and I'm the pastor I just finished
preaching well 3 minutes passed by four
minutes pass by and I go into the
potlock room and I'm like
everyone uh I can't find my daughter
everyone's like what she's been gone for
about 25 minutes and now they're like do
you have a picture of her and when I
hear
that it's done you know there is no b no
the tears are picture and I'm just
thinking of all these you know missing
person programs that I've watched and
you know she was a and then and and both
of Taun and I we're like we begin to we
we're actually crying in the
church everyone is looking everyone is
looking everywhere we call the police
don't worry Genesis is right
there we we call the police seriously
this is what's going on and let me tell
you why this is going on I'm thinking to
myself God no no no no no no no no no
God I am your I I I work for you
Lord this cannot happen here no no and
I'm just think and and this war is going
on in my head as I'm thinking anyone
ever almost have their child lost you
know the a minute seems like an eternity
it seems like an eternity and I'm there
wrestling with God in my mind and I'm
saying Lord how can this be and and
wormwood was right
there be bitter because I'm thinking now
we have to get on a plane tomorrow to uh
uh tomorrow morning or tomorrow night am
I gonna we going to get on plane without
without my daughter that's not happening
and all these thoughts running through
my
mind and then I hear we found
her and she was in one of the I don't
know 12 bathrooms in the
church they walking there and she's
singing 65 bottles of milk on the wall
65 bottles of milk no
idea what's going on that people looking
for
her and I said okay praise
God but I got a question for
you how about when the experience
doesn't turn out like
that how about how about when when the
marriage
fails how about when when when the
children turn their back on you how
about when when you know the church
member fails you how about when these
things happen how many of us struggle
saying God where are you why did you
allow this to happen you see Satan wants
to use wormwood to make us bitter
against
God not only does he seek to do that
because because check this out we can
even by the way remember
job remember what his wife told him to
do you ought to be
bitter Curse God and die just be bitter
and the Bible says job was like what are
you
foolish job did not drink the wormwood
many of us are spending our time
drinking the wormwood but check this out
check this
out wormwood has another effect because
it can lead us not only to call evil
good but it can begin to lead us to call
good
evil okay I want you to feel me on this
okay listen listen when we become so
consumed with look at the evil look at
the apostasy you know what begins to
happen
somehow everything begins to become
bitter
everything
everything he winked his eye he must be
a
Jesuit he paused when he prayed did you
hear that spiritual
formation new way just entering into the
church beloved we can become
so a bitter with the the the stuff we
see going on in the church that now
suddenly everything becomes bitter and
now God's church is
Babylon or God's church I is is is
teaching so many errors that cannot any
longer be the True Church of God he
winked he's a Jesuit he prayed long
spiritual formation I mean I believe
beloved that Satan is working so much
over time that he has many people even
afraid to
pray because I'm if I
meditate isn't that new age no well is
was David a new
Ager oh yeah because David said I what
meditate in thy
word day and
night so beloved what I'm trying to tell
you is that on one hand we we look at
the bitterness and then we respond
either by becoming bitter ourselves or
or turning into this what we think is
hyper vigilance where now everything
becomes evil and we are the only ones
that God really loves and trusts because
only we see the apostasy no one else
does and so now it is my duty and I'm
telling you let let me let me tell you
again I'm speaking frankly when when you
feel the bitterness of you know being
rejected by the church because of a
message you're preaching you that
bitterness begins to
evolve into you preaching against the
apple of God's
eye so oh you don't accept me you don't
accept my Ministry you don't accept my
message yeah the church is this is and
you know what all you begin to focus on
is the negative in the church and in
doing that you become bitter so the
devil doesn't care which ditch you fall
into he's like drink wormwood and it'll
have the same effect one way or the
other
do you
know that they
gave
Jesus wormwood to drink at the
cross oh
yeah and the Bible says when he tasted
of it and knew it was wormwood he would
not
what uh he's like I'm not drinking this
I want you to understand the
significance of
that Jesus is on the
cross he's just been betrayed not by the
world but by who his own
church his own
church was teaching doctrines that were
that were not accurate that were not
correct his own church betrays him his
own
people are spitting on him at the cross
his own people are mocking him at the
cross and they give him wormwood and
he's like not drinking
it I will not allow myself to be
infected with
bitterness do you know the result that
we read about of wormwood it caused men
to
die it's simply saying men saw the water
looked at the water said it's poisonous
I'm not going to drink of it do you know
what wormwood will eventually lead you
to do wormwood will eventually lead you
to leave God and leave the
church how many people do you know that
were once sday Adventist and left
because something bitter happened to
them 20 years ago the Elders of the
church did this to me and Satan may have
used those elders
simply for the purpose of making you
bitter and causing you to lose your
spiritual
life beloved you cannot allow no matter
how bitter it may be you cannot allow
the bitterness you see the bitterness
that you experience from others
especially within the church to lead you
to become bitter against
God follow Jesus's example on on the
cross the Bible says he refused to drink
let me tell you something when you
become bitter it changes the way you
view
scripture it changes the way you study
the Bible it I'm telling
you when you
hear
members
pastors
Ministries who are always t ending to be
negative
accusatory
bitter don't drink the cool the
wormwood don't drink the
wormwood beloved I'm not telling you yet
we ought to be concerned about our
church and about compromise and about
apostasy but you do it in a
way where you don't allow yourself to be
infected with
wormwood let me show share with you one
last thing I want you to turn with me to
the book of e uh of uh Exodus the book
of Exodus the book of Exodus you know
what Jesus prayed on the cross what did
he pray father what forgive
them wow they offer him wormwood
but instead he
prays forgive
them
wow that's the
gospel Jesus said I will not drink of a
tainted gospel I will not drink of a
tainted Fountain of water that is the
true gospel so listen Exodus
15 and verse
23 Exodus chapter 15 and verse
23 beloved I'm telling you there are
more people that will apostas eyesee
from wormwood than from any other false
Doctrine out
there yeah so spiritual formation yeah
it's a real thing uh uh uh you name the
you know new age real thing you think of
all the apostasies you can think of and
I'm telling you that wormwood is the
apostasy that will bring Mo cause most
people to drop out of God's Church
because it's one that's often backed up
by a
self-righteous
attitude and let me also mention that
your own personal failures can lead to
your own personal
wormwood that's why the devil wants you
to fail see every time you apostasis
personally every time you compromise
personally guess what if if you if you
you will get this sense of bitter
disappointment I can't believe I did
that again I can't believe I said that
again I can't believe I smoked that
again I can't believe I went there again
and time after time you get to the place
you're like you know what I am so bitter
God is not there helping me I give
up
wormwood wormwood listen Exodus 15 verse
23 are you there
and when they came to Mara they could
not drink of the Waters of Mara for they
were bitter therefore the name of it was
called Mara meaning bitter the people
murmured against Moses saying what shall
we
drink and he cried unto the Lord and the
Lord showed him a tree which when he had
cast into the waters the waters were
made sweet
okay you're wondering why I'm
smiling bitter Waters we can't drink of
it God says I want you to take a
tree I want you to take a
tree and cast that tree into the
bitterness and the waters will become
sweet again
beloved listen to
me
Christ on the cross is the sweetness of
the
Gospel when we
focus of on Christ on the
cross that which is making us
bitter will
disappear the waters will become sweet
again
your personal failures your personal
apostasies the failures of God's Church
the the the teach Whatever It Is God
says I don't want you to focus on the
bitter Waters I want you to focus on the
tree and if you focus on the tree I will
keep you from the bitter
Waters the bitter Waters kill but the
tree gives
life and so my appeal to you very simply
is this do not drink
wormwood I don't care what she did to
you 15 years
ago I don't care what he said to you
today if you allow bitterness into your
heart here closing text closing text
Hebrews 11 Hebrews chapter
11 I'm sorry Hebrews chapter 12 Hebrews
chapter 12 and verse 25
Hebrews
12 verse 15 I'm sorry verse
15 Hebrews 12
12:15 it says looking
diligently lest any man fail of the
grace of God lest any root
of give me another word
wormwood lest any root of bitterness or
wormwood springing up trouble you and
thereby
defile
many purpose of wormwood is to
defile so Satan will use whoever he can
or whatever he can to make you
bitter my appeal to you
do not drink
wormwood do not drink wormwood instead
focus on the cross Heavenly
Father it is truly
discouraging as we look at the way we
treat one another sometimes as your
People Ministry to
Ministry member to me M minister to
minister it is discouraging and
disheartening
sometimes to see the politics to see the
underhandedness that goes on within the
profess Church of
God and yet Lord you tell us do not
focus on the bitter Waters but focus on
the
tree Lord help us to keep our eyes
stayed upon
Christ because in doing that Lord we
will not be led astray by the deceptions
by the apostasies by the compromises and
at the same time Lord even though we see
them and recognize them and pray for
those involved in them we ourselves will
not become self-righteously bitter or
bitter to the point of leaving God's
church because of our own
failures Jesus refused to drink
wormwood may we too refuse to drink
wormwood help our faces to reflect the
sweetness of the Gospel not the
bitterness of
wormwood in Jesus name we pray amen